export const leads = [
  {
    id: 1,
    name: "Jane Doe",
    service: "Web Development",
    location: "New York, USA",
    budget: "$2,000",
    jobDescription: "Build a responsive website for an e-commerce store.",
    selected: true,
    responses: 2,
    price: 33,
    phone: "077*******",
    email: "J**********@gmail.com",
    details: [
      {
        question: "What are your website needs?",
        answer: "To sell products/services e.g. e-commerce",
      },
      {
        question: "What type of business is this for?",
        answer: "Sole trader/self-employed",
      },
      {
        question: "What industry do you operate in?",
        answer: "Creative industries",
      },
      {
        question: "When would you like the website to go live/be updated?",
        answer: "As soon as possible",
      },
      {
        question: "What is your estimated budget for this project?",
        answer: "Less than £250",
      },
      {
        question: "How likely are you to make a hiring decision?",
        answer: "I'm definitely going to hire someone",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    name: "John Smith",
    service: "Graphic Design",
    location: "Los Angeles, USA",
    budget: "$1,500",
    jobDescription: "Create a modern and eye-catching logo for a startup.",
    responses: 4,
    price: 33,
    phone: "079*******",
    email: "J**********@gmail.com",
    details: [
      {
        question: "What is your web design requirement?",
        answer: "Create a new website",
      },
      {
        question: "What are your website needs?",
        answer: "To advertise my business/services",
      },
      {
        question: "What type of business is this for?",
        answer: "Small business (1 - 9 employees)",
      },
      {
        question: "What industry do you operate in?",
        answer: "Shipping & Freight",
      },
      {
        question: "When would you like the website to go live/be updated?",
        answer: "Within a few weeks",
      },
      {
        question: "What is your estimated budget for this project?",
        answer: "£250 - £999",
      },
      {
        question: "How likely are you to make a hiring decision?",
        answer: "I'm likely to hire someone",
      },
      {
        question: "Additional details",
        answer:
          "Hi, I currently have a website but this new site would be to advertise new destinations that we are serving. It would be a trading as a new company name, so that's why I would like a new site.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    name: "Alice Johnson",
    service: "Social Media Marketing",
    location: "London, UK",
    budget: "$800",
    jobDescription:
      "Run a targeted social media campaign for a small business.",
    responses: 1,
    price: 33,
    phone: "077*******",
    email: "A**********@gmail.com",
    details: [
      {
        question: "What is your web design requirement?",
        answer: "Create a new website",
      },
      {
        question: "What are your website needs?",
        answer: "To advertise my business/services",
      },
      {
        question: "What type of business is this for?",
        answer: "Personal project",
      },
      {
        question: "What industry do you operate in?",
        answer: "Business services",
      },
      {
        question: "When would you like the website to go live/be updated?",
        answer: "As soon as possible",
      },
      {
        question: "What is your estimated budget for this project?",
        answer: "£1,000 - £1,999",
      },
      {
        question: "How likely are you to make a hiring decision?",
        answer: "I'm ready to hire now",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    name: "Bob Williams",
    service: "Mobile App Development",
    location: "Toronto, Canada",
    budget: "$3,500",
    jobDescription:
      "Develop a cross-platform mobile app for a fitness tracking service.",
    responses: 0,
    price: 33,
    phone: "097*******",
    email: "B**********@gmail.com",
    details: [
      {
        question: "What is your web design requirement?",
        answer: "Create a new website",
      },
      {
        question: "What are your website needs?",
        answer:
          "To advertise my business/services, To sell products/services e.g. e-commerce",
      },
      {
        question: "What type of business is this for?",
        answer: "Sole trader/self-employed",
      },
      {
        question: "What industry do you operate in?",
        answer: "Financial services",
      },
      {
        question: "When would you like the website to go live/be updated?",
        answer: "As soon as possible",
      },
      {
        question: "What is your estimated budget for this project?",
        answer: "£3,000 - £4,999",
      },
      {
        question: "How likely are you to make a hiring decision?",
        answer: "I'm ready to hire now",
      },
    ],
  },
];
